Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
To be continued...
Flame creation magic, Leo Ruggians!
Ah, is that all you've got?
I had to say, Captain, I'm very disappointed in you!
When you attacked, the mana grew thin in some places across the barrier for the briefest moment. Those were the spots I aimed for.
Man! He's awesome!
Listen to me, Radies. You have incredible talent, as well as powerful magic. But wielded without a just spirit, they are no more than savagery.
You're a monster! They were right to have expelled you!
I need to get stronger, so I can handle something like this more easily.
It's a bit early to be celebrating. The preparations must be nearly complete by now.
Time for a feast. Such lively young mana. Absolutely delicious.
Part 2
action for a while.
yearn
Thank you.
I've honed my magic, studied the enemy, made meticulous preparations, years of work, countless hours of planning for this day, for this moment.
All wasted.
How did this happen?
Nice work. Thanks for the shield.
Keep your thanks and take care of him already.
I'm on it.
Flame magic! Viral flame!
It's over!
Sir, that pile of ash won't give us any trouble now!
Very well done, both of you.
You've shown your worth as magic knights and as royalties.
Sir!
What am I doing saluting him?
No. Impossible!
I'm stronger! Royalty or not, nobody is more powerful than I am!
You'll see!
Now, flame creation magic, Leo Palma.
Get these flames off of me, damn you!
This isn't fair!
It's not over!
I'll show you!
Free me, don't prove how powerful I am!
There are a great many questions I would like to ask.
And you will answer.
But first, I'm going to take a look at your grimoire.
Wait! No!
That's mine! Don't touch it!
You have no right!
Interesting.
It seems unusually thin.
No! Leave it alone!
Unbelievable.
It only has one page.
Quit looking!
Put it down now!
One page?
That's mine!
Does this mean he can only wield a single spell?
Give it back!
Haven't you done enough?
I don't need your mockery, too!
Mockery?
I don't hear anyone laughing!
I get that you wanted people to take you seriously.
But I don't understand why you had to do it like this.
You're strong.
And you've got a ton of magic power.
But now, all that strength and power mean nothing!
You threw them away!
Come here.
I try not to get me all dirty.
Thanks.
I'll do my best.
Perhaps you could have become a great man if you had gone down a different path.
This is where the lack of a just heart has led you.
You must atone.
Will?
Are you satisfied?
A voice?
What is it?
What's wrong?
I hope you've at least learned a lesson.
Clearly your might alone was not enough to defeat a squad, Captain.
No.
I almost won.
Really?
Sometimes you cannot win, no matter how great your power.
My power, too, nears its limit.
No more acting on your own.
From now on, we proceed according to plan.
For the Master's sake.
Three cheers for the magic knights!
I knew you would save us!
Thank you!
Now then, I can practically hear Desert calling my name.
Would you care to come along?
I'll pass.
Thank you.
A nice hot bath sounds awesome right about now, huh, Char?
Heavenly.
Good job, Blue Rose Knights!
Thank you!
Captain Charlotte is just so amazing!
Not to mention beautiful, too!
Soul is cooler, though!
Ha ha ha ha!
I have a feeling this isn't over.
What do they want?
Excellent.
They're all in the designated areas.
My grimoire.
Magic?
Allow me to thank you for your service, magic knights.
What the?
Look out!
Where did the magic knights go?
They disappeared completely.
But how?
Soul's gone!
Oh, heavens!
Where are we?
I would estimate that we're at least a few hundred kilometers from the royal capital, judging by the terrain here.
They sent us away?
That's not nice!
Our enemy has taken things a step further.
I knew there was a strong spatial magic user working with them, but even so...
To do this, transporting us all would require great skill.
We have failed!
Something's wrong.
Where'd the other magic knights' mana go?
I don't know, but I can't sense it either.
I want to know how you carried out this attack.
Where are the others you're working with?
Ha ha ha.
Um, does anyone know what's happening?
Something is definitely wrong.
Those idiots fell for it hook, line, and sinker.
It was almost too easy.
And these are the greatest mages in the country?
How utterly pathetic.
I was going to play with any of the knights who escaped, but I suppose I won't get to now.
Oh well.
This place is full of young mana.
Time to start harvesting.
Ash Curse Magic.
Ash Absorbing Formation.
What is happening?
Much better.
Thanks to your generous donations, I can feel myself growing younger already.
Who knew that skin could be this smooth?
Magic!
Just let him go!
You think you're so sweet and cute, don't you?
Well, you're not!
Sal!
Eliza!
No!
Oh my.
Now there's a fine-looking specimen.
Tell me, my dear, am I beautiful?
Care to take a guess at my age?
I'm waiting.
What have you done?
You're some kind of monster!
No one calls me a monster!
No one!
No!
Ooh!
And lucky for me, this one's a beauty!
What do you say we have some fun together, lovely?
I'm not gonna let you hurt any more of these people, you old hag.
You're dead!
Oh, and lucky for me, this one's a beauty.
What do you say we have some fun together, lovely?
I'm not going to let you hurt any more of these people.
You old hag.
You're dead!
How dare you call me an old hag!
Ash curse magic!
Cheerful ash destruction!
These little shells contain all kinds of lovely curses.
The best part is you won't know what they'll do until they hit you.
Who are you and why are you here?
What are you people hoping to accomplish?
Ah, so you have enough breath to chat, do you?
Very well, your pretty face has earned you an answer.
Our mission is relatively simple.
There's a certain someone we need to get rid of.
And who would that be?
Oh, come now, you don't honestly think I would tell you.
Right, good looks only gets you so far!
There's at least one other involved in this plot besides you.
This invasion required the use of spatial magic on an immense scale.
So tell me, where is your partner?
Have they escaped already?
They may have managed to send the magic knights away from the capital,
but that doesn't mean they have the power necessary to capture it.
Nor do I believe this to be something as simple as a feint to reach the king.
You've made it clear your personal motive is revenge,
but I sense that there was a larger purpose behind the attack.
Do you want to know what we're after?
You, Fregolian Vermillion, we came for you!
For me.
But why him?
Yes, why?
Spatial magic again, eh?
Very well.
Maybe now we'll get to the bottom of this.
Strange, what is this place?
Her attacks just keep coming, and she isn't tiring at all.
The shells themselves don't do much damage, but what's inside them...
Oh dear, look at you flail.
Which of my curses has its grip on you now, I wonder?
You don't seem to be so chatty anymore.
Damn you.
My eyes, I can barely see now.
It's not just my vision.
All of my senses are fading.
Say, can you hear me?
Hello?
My hearing's almost gone now.
What kind of power does this woman have?
Are you enjoying my cheerful ash destruction spell?
It works slowly, but quite effectively.
It looks like you've lost your vision.
And your hearing too, I would guess.
Soon you won't even be able to move.
Sensory deprivation and the fear that comes with it.
That's your punishment for calling me an old hag.
The four-leaf clover.
However, I joined the Golden Dawn to live up to the expectations that came with this grimoire.
But what happens if I never can?
Four-leaf clover or not, you're still just a commoner.
Don't get cocky.
Your skills merit little attention in the Golden Dawn, village boy.
Soon enough, no one will remember your name.
I ignored the people who doubted me.
Instead, I honed my skills and worked to make myself unbeatable.
Except...
I couldn't win.
It wasn't me who defeated him.
It was a power buried in that dungeon.
When I just happened to stumble across.
A power I can't control.
No matter what I do, I can't get it to listen to me.
I couldn't even evade the spatial magic on my own.
I escaped because the power reacted.
A power I can hardly call my own.
His work may be subpar, but it's not as if we expect much of a commoner.
No, that's not it.
I don't care what they say.
That's not what really frustrates me.
Was that supposed to be aimed at me?
Here, let me show you how to aim a spell properly.
I'll make you a deal.
Grovel for me.
I might let you live if it's good enough.
Let's see how prettily you beg.
Well?
Not a chance.
Blind.
I can't see anything.
Numb, too.
I can't feel anything.
Is this the mana stream?
Mages who wield wind-based magic are particularly skilled at sensing mana.
The enemy's attack deprived Yuno of his senses.
However, with all other distractions taken away, his sensitivity to mana became even more heightened and made possible what came next.
Come on now, open that stubborn mouth of yours.
I'm not going to wait forever, you know.
Hurry up or I'll have to kill you.
There's so many things I want to know about you.
So, let's hear you beg.
Well, well, I don't hear you!
Please, just shut up.
I don't care about you or what you want.
Only one thing matters to me now.
I can't lose.
Not to Asta!
I'm not done!
Is that what I think it is?
The legendary four-leaf clover grimoire?
The mana, it's gathering!
It feels like...
No, impossible!
Is he controlling the mana?
I see now.
The spirit has been sending out mana signals this whole time.
But I relied too much on my vision and hearing.
So I wasn't able to sense them.
There's just one very important thing to know about me.
The truth is...
I would rather give my life than lose!
Win spirit magic!
Self-threat!
One chance!
I have to use the power I stole!
Aaaaaah!
It's you!
One chance!
trillion员
乾いた感情が
あの日の僕を見つめ
突き動かしてる
I can find a place to go
消えそうな光でも
闇を照らす力が
If it's cultural, love is imperative
I have to weave in it and I
Take care of your feelings
Free yourself
If there's nofiction 83 years
Non-existent energy
Don't care exactly me
Or if there's no Wenn
That's another option
That's the Pink dusl
My life is going to be
See you next time.
Closer Clips!
Birthday.
I finally figured out how to command the wind spirit.
I've decided to name you Belle and make today your birthday.
I got you a cake and everything.
Yay!
There's just one candle. I hope that's okay.
Hooray! Happy birthday, Belle.
Pretty!
Go on, make a wish, then blow it out.
Well, um...
Huh? Where did the cake go?
I found it.
Where did you send my brother?
Answer me if you want to live.
Faguleon, what happened to you?
Brother!
Black Clover, page 25.
Adversity.
Always remember to stay calm.
AHHH!
AHHHH!
AHHHH.